Good Morning, Church.
My name is Lucy Atim Hansen.
I'm originally Ugandan, living in Norway.
What brought me to The SCOAN was suicidal thoughts and different sorts of pain.
This all started when I was young.
When I was a little girl, I was about 2 and a half years old, I had my little sister,
my mum and my dad; we were four in the house.
One day, when I was 2 and a half years old, I remember I was sitting with my little sister
in the living room, playing and my dad was sitting and reading the newspaper.
My mum came from work, parked her car in the garage and passed through the kitchen.
From the kitchen, she came through the corridor with a gallon of paraffin.
I run after her and she told me to go and play with my little sister.
I went back and sat down and she went down the corridor to her bedroom.
A few minutes later, I saw smoke coming from the corridor.
I told my dad that there was smoke in the house but as a child, he didn’t take me seriously
and just said I should continue playing, that my mum was coming soon.
The next thing I knew was a scream that I can never forget because
I was such a little girl and I had never heard anyone scream like that before.
Those who were outside had already seen the fire through the roof.
The fire brigade came, the ambulance came and a neighbour came and carried us.
The biggest mistake she did was to stand there with us because she was curious to see.
They brought her out of the house; she didn’t have any skin left
but she was alive, screaming, “John, if I don’t make it, take care of my kids.”
They took her to hospital and two days later, they took us to see her at the hospital.
The only thing I knew was to listen to her voice talking, telling us that everything would be OK
but she was covered in something that I could not see her.
That was the last time I saw her.
Two days later, she died and life turned around.
After my mum died, we moved from that house to another house.
As a child, I remember that after 6 or 7 months, my dad married a new woman in the house.
Life became harder and it wasn’t only her that I suffered the rejection and abuse from.
The whole family rejected us as if the death of our mother was our fault.
Then, when I was eight years old, I couldn’t take the pain so I ran away from home.
I went to the missionaries and started working as a dish washer to survive.
I left my little sister behind and two years after, she died.
Then it was me and my dad.
My dad never cared much.
Maybe he cared but he was scared of people around him.
I had been accused of each and every thing – that I was a thief, I was the ugly one.
There is no name in this world that I didn’t get called – different types of names,
which made me grow up thinking that I was the ugliest child in the world, a thief and a killer.
With that rejection, I moved on.
I never went home again.
From there, I started my own life by working hard.
I had children after being raped many times.
I was only four years old and I was raped by a grown up man.
I couldn’t say it to anybody.
I lived in the pain and I moved in it
until my auntie, a friend came with her husband from Norway and he said he wanted to adopt me.
Sorry, our sister, it is quite a terrible situation and experience;
before you go any further - could you just tell us, the death of your mum,
the encounter you had after your father married a new wife,
and when you were 8 years old, your younger sister died as well -
with all these terrible circumstances, what happened to you at the end of the day?
It affected my life mentally – with all this stress and torture, no respect, nobody liked me.
I developed headaches and could go with these headaches for three months non-stop.
I didn’t eat and go to the toilet normally.
I could go for three weeks without going to the toilet.
I didn’t go to the toilet unless I took tablets.
Suddenly they said I had a heart problem.
They took me everywhere, for MRIs I don’t know how many times.
I had depression and was admitted to hospital and locked up because they said I was crazy.
There was no treatment and they found a lot of sicknesses in me every day.
I had migraines every month.
Even last month, I suffered from migraines.
I had 40 bottox injections to cool my migraines down.
I could go for months, day and night.
When I went to Norway, everything went OK.
I started to go to school.
I started to learn very fast.
I started to get a small job and was working, going to school and earning my pocket money.
Then, suddenly, my aunt divorced.
When they were going through the divorce and separation, she left and I had to go with her.
During that time, I thought I was safe but I wasn’t.
Mrs Lucy Atim Hansen
Deliverance Testimony
It is indeed a pathetic situation.
We believe it is all cause for joy, because the end is sweet.
We know all your suffering, pain and agony have come to an end.
I'm sorry.
People of God, I wasn't safe.
I would be at home and suddenly, my aunt would come back home with a guest.
And that ‘guest’ was a terrible experience for me.
I would be sent to ‘serve’ that person, whether I wanted it or not.
Now, think about it – men that you don’t know that it’s going to happen but it will happen.
It indeed happened – four to five times; it was terrible.
That is why I said that all my life I had been raped, rejected and felt like nothing.
These are the things that have been in my mind that I’m ugly and completely nothing.
Among those men who came to me, there was a man who God helped me through.
He saw the pain in me and said, “I don’t understand; what is this?
You are crying and in pieces, what is wrong?
I know you don’t want to do this; I can’t do this. I don’t have the heart; I cannot do it.
Don’t be scared of me, I’m going to help you. You are in pain; I can see it and feel it.
Don’t be scared; I won’t hurt you.”
That was how he talked to me and said that he would help me.
The man called my uncle and told him, “If this girl gets killed or falls into problems, as her father,
you will be responsible for it. Come here and let me tell you what is going on.”
So, they met and after the meeting,
the man said he was going to pay for an apartment for me, for two years.
Indeed, he found an apartment for me, I moved in and he paid for the apartment.
He did it like as a father would; he helped in different ways.
He said it was too painful the day he saw me; he wanted to see me happy and
he was ready to stand and protect me if anything happened to me, which he did.
I started going to school from my apartment, I found a job and was working part-time.
I took a hair dressing course.
About six to seven months later, I was working together with my neighbour’s wife;
we became friends, the woman was Danish.
My husband had grown up together with her husband but he lived far away in a village.
He came to visit my neighbours and I was there grilling together with the lady I worked with.
So, we met but we didn’t exchange contact details at once.
For about a year, we would talk now and again as he lived far away.
After that year, things became serious and he told me that he wanted to marry me.
I didn’t trust him but he said I should trust him
and that meeting me was the best thing that happened to him.
He said I was ‘over kind’.
I said, “OK but I don’t know if your family will accept me because I am dark skinned”.
He said, “If they love me, they will love you and if they don’t love me, they will reject you.
And if they reject you, they reject me too.”
OK, you mean it was in the house of that Danish friend where you met with your current husband.
Yes.
OK
Before you go any further from there, could you just tell us...
You made us to understand that right from the age of 4, you were abused to the age of 15 by unknown men.
Could you tell us what was the consequence of this abuse?
The abuse happened in different ways.
Back home, from 13 years old, I had a baby boy.
Before I was 14 years old, I had another one.
By the age of 15-16 years old, I had three children.
I was 16 and these children till now, are back home.
Then, you were not married.
I was not married.
I moved in with my husband and we have been together now for 16 years.
We have a girl together.
Could you tell us; in the course of these terrible experiences -
was there anything you were addicted to?
When I was 10 years old, I started to smoke and I became addicted to smoking.
I could smoke more than 40 cigarettes a day.
Finally, with me being sick here and there, at times, I would want to run away from home.
Whenever I saw lots of snow, I wanted to run and bury my head inside it.
I would go crazy in the house.
My husband did everything he could and I would tell him every day
that it was not material things that I wanted but rather my freedom.
I told him that I was not free, that I was in pain.
Then one day, while on YouTube, I suddenly came across Emmanuel TV
where I was surprised to see a lot of people being delivered.
I said, "My God".
I saw people in situations like mine and worse
and said to myself that this man would be the one to take me out of my pain,
that I had to look for him.
Mrs Lucy Atim Hansen
Deliverance Testimony
From that day, I started to watch Emmanuel TV every single day.
I could sit and watch it for the whole day.
My husband would travel a lot.
When he was not at home, I would not go to the bedroom; I would sleep in the living room.
We don’t have Emmanuel TV but I would watch it through YouTube.
I would sit and watch it the whole night and day.
My husband and children would tell me, “You with this TV – you are going crazy”.
Even the kids...
I would tell them that this man was the man who was going to make me happy.
I told them that I wanted to come here; that was eight months ago.
By the time I wanted to come here, things started to get worse.
Firstly, my husband told me that I had to make a choice – to have a holiday house in Africa
or go to The SCOAN.
I told him that if he wanted to see me happy, I wanted to go to The SCOAN.
I said if the house was meant for me in Africa, I would have it in the name of Jesus
but that first, I had to look for my freedom.
He responded that he wanted to see me happy.
Put your hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Your husband said, "I promised to build you a mansion back in Uganda.
Now, make a choice between these two: acquiring this mansion and going to The SCOAN here in Nigeria."
The woman made the best, wisest choice.
She told the husband, "Look, I prefer to go to The SCOAN and get my freedom.
The house is a secondary issue. The primary thing is my freedom."
The husband said, "Well, let it be according to your wish. I will prepare your passport and visa."
Not long after that, the DHL brought her passport and visa, right to her house.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Finally, when your visa and passport came to your door post, what happened?
Three days later, he told me that I had to pack, that I said I was going on Friday,
so, by Saturday, I would be in Nigeria.
On Saturday, on my way to the airport, I was smoking.
When I came out of the airport, it was like I was on fire
because I had been on the flight for so long.
I took my things out of the airport and on standing there,
the driver asked me if he could put my luggage in his car.
I said no, that I had to fulfil this: I smoked three cigarettes at the same time.
When I arrived at the hotel, I smoked another cigarette before being taken to my room.
I came downstairs and by the pool, I smoked another two sticks before paying the driver off.
The taxi driver asked, “Madam, are you not smoking too much?”
I responded, “What is too much? This is not too much; I haven’t smoked for many hours”.
Then, he left.
For the whole night, I couldn’t sleep because I wanted to come here.
That was the time that I smoked even more than usual.
For the whole Saturday night, I was smoking.
I didn't sleep, I was awake.
At 3am, I prepared myself; I told the taxi to come at four.
At 4am, he was there.
I was outside with a cup of coffee and a smoke.
I had already smoked ten by that time.
When there is something that you want so badly,
there will also be many things that will want to stop you.
It was hard to come in but when I came in, I sat over there.
I was praying and suddenly the man of God came in.
When he came in, he was talking to people and I began to sleep.
I did not hear a word he was saying because I was sleeping.
I went outside and poured water on myself but I was still sleepy.
I asked myself, “What is this?”
The time I woke up, he was on the gallery, delivering people.
I started panicking.
I was looking forward to this but I was panicking.
I was telling a man that I needed to go outside and get some fresh air.
He told me that the man of God was already here.
I said no, that I would make it.
It was not because I wanted fresh air but I was panicking and wanted to smoke.
I wanted to smoke because I was scared.
The moment I was talking with him, I heard people around me making noises.
I closed my eyes and held myself like this.
Then suddenly I felt something like a hammer hit my head, people of God.
Mrs Lucy Atim Hansen
Deliverance Testimony
It was not a touch, it was a hammer.
Then I was like, “Who hit me like that?”
I touched my head because I thought my head was smashed.
I screamed, that was the only thing I knew.
The next thing I knew I was somewhere here on those stairs.
They were telling me, “It’s OK, sister, calm down”.
I was in awe but also so mad that I felt I could tear them into pieces.
As the day went, my anger subsided.
Viewers all over the world, watch the screen of your TV;
that was exactly what the sister is narrating as part of her experience.
She came and sat down in the church.
When the man of God was about to give messages of prophecy and was moving forward,
close to where she was, she started to feel terrible heat inside of her,
to the extent that she was telling the person next to her that she wanted to leave the church premises.
The person sitting next to her said, "You don't need to go out. The man of God is coming closer".
She said she needed to find fresh air.
That was exactly, without being told, when the evil spirit was actually troubling her,
because darkness and light have no meeting point.
Exactly in the moment the man of God came close to her, she felt uncomfortable.
When the man of God laid his hand on her, the evil spirit started manifesting
as you can see on the screen of your TV.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God.
After that touch, I got my deliverance but I was still mad.
Later in the evening, I was prayed for again and felt the same bang on my head.
I said, “God, do I have to be beaten many times like this today?”
It was late in the evening when the programme finished.
The workers told the man of God that my hotel was very far, close to the airport.
He instructed them that I should not go to my hotel but that I should stay in the church
because at that late time, it was risky.
They prepared a nice place for me with a nice bed.
Normally, I did not just fall asleep
but I was so tired that I just fell on my bed with the same clothes and slept.
Suddenly, something just lifted me up.
People of God, I was in the air like this, hanging.
I said, "Wow, what is that?"
I was so heavy, on the roof of the house
and when I suddenly woke up, I dropped onto the bed again.
I was scared and something came out of me!
I could feel it.
It was like I was two persons and someone pulled me up and left.
I turned around to look at where it was going and I was in awe and went back to sleep again.
A few minutes later, it happened again up to three times and I went back to sleep again.
The following day on a Monday, I went back to the hotel.
When I reached the hotel, I said, “Now that I am not in the church, I can take a smoke”.
When I tried to smoke, it was not tasting the same.
I said, "Ah".
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
It is indeed a wonderful experience.
I thought that it may have been because I had not been smoking.
I was in the church the whole day and night and I did not smoke.
I went up, got a coffee, went to the pool and tried to light a cigarette but it was not working.
The driver was asking me why I was throwing away the whole cigarette.
I told him that it did not taste the same and that maybe I was delivered from smoking as well.
He replied that he thought so too.
Then I said that if I was delivered from smoking and I try to force myself to smoke,
then it is like I am testing, or trying God that if He was real, He should take it away from me.
He has already taken it away from me, then I will not try it again.
I had 12 sealed packets of cigarettes.
Each packet had 30 cigarettes.
I took all of them and four lighters to where there was a big ash tray outside the hotel,
left them there, got into a taxi and came here.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
To God be the glory.
At the end of the day, you are letting us know that right now, as you are talking,
you have stopped smoking.
I haven’t smoked since Sunday.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God.
God lives in this house.
He is alive.
I tried to attain deliverance in many kinds of churches
but I have never received this kind of touch.
Usually after finishing a church service, I would go outside and smoke or go to the hospital
but since I came here, I now eat and go to the toilet normally which was not the case before.
I do everything normally. I don’t have the urge to smoke.
This is someone who would smoke every five minutes. I don’t have the feeling to smoke.
When I pass people outside there who are smoking,
I don’t have the feeling to do the same.
What about the migraine and depression?
I don’t have depression and I feel happy.
Secondly, the man of God has been treating me like his baby.
This is the kind of treatment that I have never had.
He gave me a place to stay.
Could you just explain to us the pictures we can see on the notice board.
As you can see here, this is my husband.
This is my first son.
This is the second.
This is the third.
This is the fourth.
This is the last.
As you can see on this board - this is a letter from my doctor,
stating that I was undergoing treatment for migraine and psychiatric treatment.
Every third month, I had to get 40 to 50 injections inside my nerves
and at the back of my head to relax my muscles.
This is what you see here.
But after you were delivered, old things passed away, all things have become new.
Yes.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ.
I had a lot of medications that I took every day, like six to seven
but I have not been feeling any pain.
I had two operations on my right shoulder and was preparing to go for a third one
but I do not feel any pain; I can sleep without pain.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ.
To God be the glory.
Finally, we thank the Lord Almighty for setting you free from this trouble,
taking you out of the kingdom of darkness into the kingdom of light.
Viewers around the world and in the church, the only advice I can give you is one thing:
If you see a child looking for your shoulder to rest her or his head on, please take that child as yours.
Respect that child as you respect your own.
Give them love because you do not know tomorrow.
God will reward you.
Take care of the little ones.
Don’t let them suffer.
Thank you, let's clap for Jesus Christ!
We strongly believe that that piece of advice is coming from your past experience in life.
We believe you are rejuvenated, old things passed away, all things have become new.
We thank God Almighty for what the Lord Jesus has done in your life.
We pray that your deliverance, healing and breakthrough will remain permanent, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Go and make the Word of God the standard for your life,
and as you go and do so, always have it at the back of your mind, that better is not good enough,
the best is always yet to come.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 15/11/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 01/12/2018